<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>r/DenverProtests</title>
    <link>https://old.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/</link>
    <description>Reddit posts from r/DenverProtests</description>
    <managingEditor> (r/DenverProtests)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 03:55:38 -0700</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Fist Bumping proud boys?</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/k0mgte/fist_bumping_proud_boys/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>So are we fist-bumping proud boys while continuing to shame our fellow protesters, like those who voted for biden or those who see property destruction as a form of protest (similar to the boston tea party, stonewall riots, women&#39;s suffrage movement, berlin wall, etc)? Asking for a friend?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/SwimPhillips"> /u/SwimPhillips </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/k0mgte/fist_bumping_proud_boys/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/k0mgte/fist_bumping_proud_boys/">[comments]</a></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/k0mgte/fist_bumping_proud_boys/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 23:02:25 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fist bumping proud boys?</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/k0m7h0/fist_bumping_proud_boys/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>For months now, I&#39;ve watched &quot;woke&quot; people shame white protesters. Consistently telling them that they are not part of the BLM movement because they vote for Biden, or break windows, or yell things at the cops. Shaming people for wearing helmets during protests when they shoot rubber bullets at our heads. People who have been showing up on a weekly basis to protest racial injustice, despite being accused of &quot;taking over the movement&quot; on the bullhorn all the fucking time. </p> <p>That&#39;s all fine.</p> <p>But after dealing with all that shit, it kinda pisses me off to see these same people having a &quot;civil discussion&quot; with the proud boys, the first freaking time we encounter them in denver. The same group of PB that assaulted our fellow protesters in broad daylight in Fort Collins. Then after a 20 min discussion, everyone is fist-bumping them like racism has suddenly ended in the world. Later that night, one of those same people (POC) is still shaming protesters actually dedicated to the movement. I&#39;m sitting here like &quot;wheres my 20 min conversation and fist bump, I&#39;ve been here since June and... oh yeah I&#39;ve never been part of a white supremacist organization&quot;... nope I&#39;m just the asshole with the helmet. So are Denver BLM leaders and proud boys gonna get together to protest &quot;destructive&quot; antifa? cuz that&#39;s kinda what it feels like. All types of fucked up</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/SwimPhillips"> /u/SwimPhillips </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/k0m7h0/fist_bumping_proud_boys/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/k0m7h0/fist_bumping_proud_boys/">[comments]</a></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/k0m7h0/fist_bumping_proud_boys/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 22:43:03 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documentation of Homeless Sweeps, the tactics, and the city staff who help make them happen.</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/k0kvjj/documentation_of_homeless_sweeps_the_tactics_and/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<table> <tr><td> <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/k0kvjj/documentation_of_homeless_sweeps_the_tactics_and/"> <img src="https://b.thumbs.redditmedia.com/Cm8TQPeSL1d2to7vcBjynkiPyj0YyJc6Tba6kd9385Q.jpg" alt="Documentation of Homeless Sweeps, the tactics, and the city staff who help make them happen." title="Documentation of Homeless Sweeps, the tactics, and the city staff who help make them happen." /> </a> </td><td> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/IntellectPress"> /u/IntellectPress </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCE5w3HzHX8TlU7UiFiG3BRg/videos">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/k0kvjj/documentation_of_homeless_sweeps_the_tactics_and/">[comments]</a></span> </td></tr></table>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/k0kvjj/documentation_of_homeless_sweeps_the_tactics_and/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 21:11:31 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causes of concern</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jzp6pd/causes_of_concern/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>What’s up y’all. It’s always a privilege to see you all at the GAs I’m able to attend. I appreciate your continued commitment. </p> <p>I would like a list of causes that mean something to you all. If the cause is already mentioned in the thread then I’m sure there is another you can think of. </p> <p>Everyone shouldn’t be marching. I’ve been amongst many of you for some time. You all have incredible skillsets. Many of them are not known. </p> <p>A community (commune) consists people of many skills and capabilities. Many cultures and beliefs. </p> <p>One working class!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Bat_Forsaken"> /u/Bat_Forsaken </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jzp6pd/causes_of_concern/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jzp6pd/causes_of_concern/">[comments]</a></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jzp6pd/causes_of_concern/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 13:00:32 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s happening the week of November 23 - 29</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jza8a8/whats_happening_the_week_of_november_23_29/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Please see our <a href="https://mailfence.com/pub/cal/denverprotestsdaily?a=1">new calendar</a> for the most complete list of upcoming vetted events.</p> <p>Events are color coded as follows:</p> <ul> <li>red: rally/protest/march</li> <li>purple: campaign (an event allowing activity spanning across several days)</li> <li>blue: government meeting</li> <li>yellow: education/training</li> <li>green: news</li> <li>orange: panel</li> <li>black: vigil</li> <li>pink: mutual aid</li> </ul> <h1>Wiki</h1> <p>To avoid repeating too much information from day to day, we&#39;ve created the beginnings of a wiki <a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/wiki/index">here</a>. Your feedback is much needed, as this is my (TaroPeril&#39;s) first experience with a reddit wiki. It contains links to livestreamers, your rights as a protestor, and more.</p> <h1>News</h1> <p>Please see <a href="https://twitter.com/nocapcoalition/status/1325867813215428608?s=21">this online fundraiser</a> to put together Mutual Aid/Winter Care Packages to distribute to our houseless neighbors in the Denver area! You can also <a href="https://no-capcoalition.org/events">sign up here</a> to volunteer to organize and distribute the packages.</p> <h1>Notable Events</h1> <h2>November 23</h2> <p><strong>4:30 PM - 6:30 PM</strong> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2812391055659964">Winter Survival – Full Court Press</a> (Facebook event)</p> <blockquote> <p><em>Organized by:</em> Coach MK Fleming and Wall of Moms Denver<br/> <em>Location:</em> 1431 Bannock St, Denver, CO 80202<br/> <em>Host-provided information:</em> Mayor Hancock is a disgrace, refusing to keep his campaign promise to assist the unhoused, and has unleashed a reign of terror on the most vulnerable in the form of sweeps, wasting our tax dollars during an economic recession. NO MORE. We need to be inside the meeting screaming at our reps and outside the building demonstrating <a href="/u/DenverCityCouncil">u/DenverCityCouncil</a>&#39;s utter failure to legislate. Community leaders will be demonstrating how to make survival items for the unhoused while I curse about how unnecessary this should be and demand that City Council press Hancock for #SolutionsNotSweeps in the 2021 budget, the first step to #defundthepolice and reallocate precious dollars to be invested in community SOLUTIONS.<br/> <em>Type of Event:</em> Rally/March</p> </blockquote> <p><strong>5:30 PM</strong> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/CH0fhfyJL8e/">Melanated Mic Night</a> (Instagram Post)</p> <blockquote> <p><em>Organized by:</em> Community-organized </p> <p><em>Location:</em> Instagram Live </p> <p><em>Host-provided information:</em> This Monday #melanatedmicnight will be hosting live from our new Instagram account! @melanatedmicnight we are really excited for this live stream with our special guest Sky Roosevelt-Morris |White Mtn N’dee/Shawnee| from @denverfreedomskool We’re excited to see you all tune in for conversations on Thanks-taking and more</p> <p><em>Type of Event:</em> Arts/Education</p> </blockquote> <h3>November 27</h3> <p><strong>5:30 PM</strong> <a href="https://twitter.com/anarky_astrid/status/1330657836796424193">Black Friday Mutual Aid Collection &amp; Distro</a> (Twitter post)</p> <blockquote> <blockquote> <p><em>Organized by:</em> Community-organized</p> <p><em>Location:</em> Civic Center Park</p> <p><em>Host-provided information:</em> Support your unhoused neighbors! Bring winter clothing, tarps, tents, clay pots, tealights/candles, trash bags, and cardboard</p> <p><em>Type of Event:</em> Mutual Aid</p> </blockquote> </blockquote> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/denverprotestsdaily"> /u/denverprotestsdaily </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jza8a8/whats_happening_the_week_of_november_23_29/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jza8a8/whats_happening_the_week_of_november_23_29/">[comments]</a></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jza8a8/whats_happening_the_week_of_november_23_29/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 20:48:04 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join us on Black Friday, 11/27 at 5:30PM in Civic Center Park</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jz6ylw/join_us_on_black_friday_1127_at_530pm_in_civic/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<table> <tr><td> <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jz6ylw/join_us_on_black_friday_1127_at_530pm_in_civic/"> <img src="https://b.thumbs.redditmedia.com/Dsmn8b8x6JfnQ-5sED9QAzE-cE5lMK5-pnkx-9yLSIc.jpg" alt="Join us on Black Friday, 11/27 at 5:30PM in Civic Center Park" title="Join us on Black Friday, 11/27 at 5:30PM in Civic Center Park" /> </a> </td><td> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/anarkybarbie"> /u/anarkybarbie </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/gallery/jz6ylw">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jz6ylw/join_us_on_black_friday_1127_at_530pm_in_civic/">[comments]</a></span> </td></tr></table>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jz6ylw/join_us_on_black_friday_1127_at_530pm_in_civic/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 17:21:19 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protester Arrest Today</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jyoxek/protester_arrest_today/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Can I get a confirmation on a bail arrangement?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/tigre12345"> /u/tigre12345 </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jyoxek/protester_arrest_today/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jyoxek/protester_arrest_today/">[comments]</a></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jyoxek/protester_arrest_today/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 20:45:01 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interesting read....</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jy6u05/interesting_read/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><a href="https://jamestown.org/program/antifas-denver-shooting-new-trends-in-left-wing-political-violence-syrian-connections-and-sub-cultures/">https://jamestown.org/program/antifas-denver-shooting-new-trends-in-left-wing-political-violence-syrian-connections-and-sub-cultures/</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/ReformedWindowlicker"> /u/ReformedWindowlicker </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jy6u05/interesting_read/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jy6u05/interesting_read/">[comments]</a></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jy6u05/interesting_read/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:30:07 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Open Letter to Denver Regarding Black Bloc</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jxv4c8/an_open_letter_to_denver_regarding_black_bloc/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Black bloc is a tactic. Let me say that again: black bloc is a tactic. You know what that means black bloc is <strong>not</strong>? A dogmatic way of existing at any and all protests that occur.</p> <p>Sometimes, individuals who wear black bloc engage in riotous behavior. Sometimes, they don&#39;t. While black bloc has tended to be used as an excuse to break shit and get away with it – primarily by white folks – that&#39;s not true for all individuals who engage in the black bloc tactic.</p> <p>Black bloc originated in W. Germany in 1980-81. So to anyone critiquing this tactic for primarily being used by white people, you&#39;re probably onto something since the tactic has white European origins. It came out of mass poverty that the German government refused to do anything about, and poor people decided to take action (namely through the squatters and Autonomen [Autonomist] movements).</p> <p>Property tends to get destroyed at actions when the black bloc tactic is utilized. This is partially part of the allure of black bloc. Individuals involved in black bloc actions tend to see no point in reforming a system they view as “too far gone,” so they act in ways that may ultimately lead to the destruction of the system itself (read: smashing shit). </p> <p>Now, don&#39;t get me wrong, I love some good old property destruction as much as the next person with anarchist tendencies … but it becomes a huge problem when property destruction at actions steals the limelight (read: co-option) from black and brown folks who the action was actually meant to prioritize. What do I mean? Break shit. Yes, 100%. But check your privilege on <strong>when you choose to break said shit, and consider how you breaking shit might be harming the movement for black and brown lives more than helping it.</strong> </p> <p>It seems to me that in the age of police snatching random individuals from crowds of protestors, it doesn&#39;t actually matter whether the individual they snatched did or did not engage in riotous behavior. They got got. And once the cops got you, it doesn&#39;t matter a single flying fuck whether you broke the windows of the Quiznos or if it was someone else. You&#39;re probably gonna be the one to face the consequences for that. And more often than not, these people who get snatched are black and brown. Not to say white folks don&#39;t get snatched, because they do, but obviously it is disproportionately black and brown bodies that are sacrificed and punished for engaging in political dissent. Fellow whites: we have no choice but to be better if we are going to continue operating as if we are helping in any way, shape or form.</p> <p>So let&#39;s move on from property destruction, <strong>which to be clear I am not saying is inherently wrong … just that property destruction absolutely needs to be strategic and not cause more harm than good to the movement as a whole.</strong> Ok, anyway.</p> <p>Why the hell would anyone wear black bloc and go to all the trouble of protecting their identity and trying to stay anonymous if they <strong>weren&#39;t</strong> going to engage in riotous behavior? A super fucking fair question. For the sake of transparency and possibly serving as an example, let&#39;s dive in.</p> <p>I have gone out in black bloc multiple times over the course of the summer and fall, and have not engaged in smashing shit (no matter how badly I may have wanted to at different times). I didn&#39;t start out that way, and it hasn&#39;t been every single action I&#39;ve gone to … but nonetheless, I am one of those [white] people who has worn black bloc at actions. Prior to the George Floyd uprising, I had never worn black bloc to an action. I was organizing with Extinction Rebellion Denver, doing the whole nonviolent direct action thing, and showing my face at every meeting, training, action I attended.</p> <p>But something changed for me, and I&#39;m gonna go out on a limb and say for a lot of people, after witnessing the first night of the George Floyd protests. Or, the first few days / weeks for that matter. Looking back, I think I genuinely believed we were transitioning into a completely different protest atmosphere. Walking around the streets of downtown Denver, seeing insane amounts of people out chanting, taking over the streets, breaking shit, lighting things on fire, getting tear gassed, fighting with cops … I thought the revolution was finally here. Straight up. And I&#39;m willing to accept how naive acknowledging that will make me look. </p> <p>The truth we probably all knew to be true, at least deep down anyway, is that this revolutionary moment was just that: a moment. That the feeling of revolution was fleeting. Not to say the movement is dead, because it&#39;s not. Just that, to my own and probably a few others chagrin, Denver CO is not at nor are we anywhere close to this insurrectionary / revolutionary moment we all have wet dreams about. And if that&#39;s the case, then perhaps the black bloc tactic is not necessarily viable or appropriate at this time.</p> <p>That aside, my reflection as of late is that after witnessing the war zone that downtown Denver became, I sincerely felt that it was time I started taking security culture far more seriously – from how I showed up to actions, to my online presence / use of VPNs or Tor, to leaving phones / computers / bluetooth devices turned off and far, far away when engaging in any sort of risky discussions. Incorporating black bloc was one of the main ways I tried to take this all more seriously.</p> <p>I felt that protecting my identity at actions was one of the most important things I could do to avoid getting arrested, doxxed, or otherwise targeted by police and / or fascists. And I&#39;m still concerned about those things. I saw images of protestors in Portland decked out in black bloc and tactical gear (a discussion for another time) and was under the impression that Denver needed to be more like Portland. They seemed to be this ideal that I, and many others, held up as what we should all strive for. So much so that I and many others have even made this almost holy-feeling-trek to Portland to see what they&#39;re up to and what we can learn from them and bring back to Denver. (I&#39;m aware many people outside our community have also gone to Portland to learn from them.) </p> <p>To be clear, <strong>I am not critiquing the idea of learning from other communities / movements</strong>. I am critiquing this premise that many of us seemed to have that we needed to be more like Portland, this premise that Portland was doing everything right that the rest of us couldn&#39;t figure out. And for myself, part of that was unintentionally absorbing and internalizing black bloc more as a dogma than as a tactic. I think this is a common occurrence – conflating tactics with dogmas – and in fact that was an issue I saw in Extinction Rebellion in regard to nonviolence and that we all talked about quite a lot. <strong>Any tactic will become a problem when it transcends that form and becomes a dogma</strong>. At least that&#39;s how I feel.</p> <p>And I do think that this movement has a place for black bloc to be used as a tactic. At least, I think it probably will eventually. But for now, I&#39;m not sure we&#39;re there yet. There&#39;s still so many people who either don&#39;t know what black bloc is or who have some serious concerns about it. Where we stand today, wearing black bloc may put individuals who do so at a higher risk of arrest by targeting themselves as “ungovernable” or “anarchists” to cops. And more than that, it seems to me that right now <strong>what is needed is the ability to build trust within the local [protest] community</strong>. And I think perhaps I and some of my comrades have impeded that trust-building process by trying to force the black bloc tactic onto our local situation. </p> <p>Thanks for reading if you made it the whole way through. These are just some beginning thoughts of mine on the use of the black bloc tactic. My perspective on this has been evolving pretty consistently over the course of the last few months, and particularly over the course of the last few weeks. I&#39;m hoping we can engage in some kind of “community discussion” (remembering that online discussions aren&#39;t substitutes for real-ass community) about this topic. If you super disagree with me, that&#39;s cool and you&#39;re allowed to and I&#39;d love to hear what you&#39;re thinking. If you agree with me entirely, that&#39;s also cool. If you think I missed some crucial points, you&#39;re probably right and I&#39;d love to hear them.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/lochjessnewm"> /u/lochjessnewm </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jxv4c8/an_open_letter_to_denver_regarding_black_bloc/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jxv4c8/an_open_letter_to_denver_regarding_black_bloc/">[comments]</a></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jxv4c8/an_open_letter_to_denver_regarding_black_bloc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 11:57:48 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fences are ugly, it&#39;s time to beautify our city with our expressions of pain</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jxq4dt/fences_are_ugly_its_time_to_beautify_our_city/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Beginning on &#39;Consumerism Friday&#39; aka &#39;Black Friday&#39; all members of the community are encouraged to come to put up art on the fence around Veterans Memorial Park located between Broadway, Lincoln, Colfax and 14th St. Before the erection of a barrier fence this summer, over 300 people were living in the park. For the last 5 months fences have been the response to calls for reallocating funds from the police to agencies designed to provide social services. The Gov and Mayor respond with fences and violence. Now is the time to create a visual statement, to remember our pain and loss and to send 2020 out with a finger to the face. Let&#39;s make Denver beautiful by turning these fences into memorials for those that left before us.<br/> This memorial could be continued through New Years and even expand to the excess of 50 locations where fencing and distances between us are the new solutions to communicating and working through our problems. </p> <p>When at the fence, please be considerate of Covid responsibilities as elders and at risk populations share space in community.<br/> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1271684576538967">https://www.facebook.com/events/1271684576538967</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/cuttheplastic"> /u/cuttheplastic </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jxq4dt/fences_are_ugly_its_time_to_beautify_our_city/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jxq4dt/fences_are_ugly_its_time_to_beautify_our_city/">[comments]</a></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jxq4dt/fences_are_ugly_its_time_to_beautify_our_city/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 07:37:32 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back in June</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jx9xeu/back_in_june/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<table> <tr><td> <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jx9xeu/back_in_june/"> <img src="https://b.thumbs.redditmedia.com/cEOtT_tjj8B9l9KIUk2oK5_cG7Sdo-GfjWwpF809zNQ.jpg" alt="Back in June" title="Back in June" /> </a> </td><td> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Philly-South-Paw"> /u/Philly-South-Paw </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://i.redd.it/clk3rnjv49061.jpg">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jx9xeu/back_in_june/">[comments]</a></span> </td></tr></table>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jx9xeu/back_in_june/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 12:55:43 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saturday on Capitol Hill at 1 P. M.</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jx8dey/saturday_on_capitol_hill_at_1_p_m/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<table> <tr><td> <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jx8dey/saturday_on_capitol_hill_at_1_p_m/"> <img src="https://b.thumbs.redditmedia.com/7GaP5398W5GgpXLL7bsjJgDIv6lNH7GRDMlzqCRkF1g.jpg" alt="Saturday on Capitol Hill at 1 P. M." title="Saturday on Capitol Hill at 1 P. M." /> </a> </td><td> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/madespeciallyforthis"> /u/madespeciallyforthis </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/gallery/jx8dey">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jx8dey/saturday_on_capitol_hill_at_1_p_m/">[comments]</a></span> </td></tr></table>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jx8dey/saturday_on_capitol_hill_at_1_p_m/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 11:36:25 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Found this in an Anarchy themed vaporwave art group, thought you guys would like.</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jwu5zs/found_this_in_an_anarchy_themed_vaporwave_art/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<table> <tr><td> <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jwu5zs/found_this_in_an_anarchy_themed_vaporwave_art/"> <img src="https://b.thumbs.redditmedia.com/TC4HynOR883cZe-goBe-WyQJ61fcVuKqLLOCB5OkSYY.jpg" alt="Found this in an Anarchy themed vaporwave art group, thought you guys would like." title="Found this in an Anarchy themed vaporwave art group, thought you guys would like." /> </a> </td><td> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Anon_Resistance"> /u/Anon_Resistance </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://i.redd.it/2ruz3rwzx3061.jpg">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jwu5zs/found_this_in_an_anarchy_themed_vaporwave_art/">[comments]</a></span> </td></tr></table>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jwu5zs/found_this_in_an_anarchy_themed_vaporwave_art/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 19:28:19 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#WeAreOne Solidarity action Denver are we going to represent for this one?</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jwu1js/weareone_solidarity_action_denver_are_we_going_to/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<table> <tr><td> <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jwu1js/weareone_solidarity_action_denver_are_we_going_to/"> <img src="https://b.thumbs.redditmedia.com/9vCiHnVkrIcNIn2pEnruIsKz5TUS4hZH9GS4_MDy9TQ.jpg" alt="#WeAreOne Solidarity action Denver are we going to represent for this one?" title="#WeAreOne Solidarity action Denver are we going to represent for this one?" /> </a> </td><td> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Anon_Resistance"> /u/Anon_Resistance </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://kolektiva.media/videos/watch/cdd6caeb-415f-4590-88ef-47f964dde164">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jwu1js/weareone_solidarity_action_denver_are_we_going_to/">[comments]</a></span> </td></tr></table>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jwu1js/weareone_solidarity_action_denver_are_we_going_to/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 19:20:55 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven arrested this morning, #StopTheSweeps</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jvw5x9/seven_arrested_this_morning_stopthesweeps/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<table> <tr><td> <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jvw5x9/seven_arrested_this_morning_stopthesweeps/"> <img src="https://b.thumbs.redditmedia.com/XFdBiL96N2rK1hop4G81prcdHpKXSmIHkDZ1wJd4ZvM.jpg" alt="Seven arrested this morning, #StopTheSweeps" title="Seven arrested this morning, #StopTheSweeps" /> </a> </td><td> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/demonni"> /u/demonni </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://twitter.com/AlleyShirt/status/1328706036325376000">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jvw5x9/seven_arrested_this_morning_stopthesweeps/">[comments]</a></span> </td></tr></table>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jvw5x9/seven_arrested_this_morning_stopthesweeps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 09:36:03 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>True Leadership!</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jvosnf/true_leadership/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I’m not a fan of imperialist wars. The following are examples of decentralized leadership/command. The soldiers lead! No lazy delegating. If someone on the team fucked up-That means you fucked up.</p> <p>Extreme Ownership!</p> <p><a href="https://youtu.be/KSW7LQaFHTg">https://youtu.be/KSW7LQaFHTg</a></p> <p><a href="https://youtu.be/8f0f4t1QXro">https://youtu.be/8f0f4t1QXro</a></p> <p><a href="https://youtu.be/cQCIpieOkak">https://youtu.be/cQCIpieOkak</a></p> <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cQCIpieOkak">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cQCIpieOkak</a></p> <p><a href="https://www.human-synergistics.com.au/resources/content/2017/11/01/12-achievement-principles-in-extreme-ownership">https://www.human-synergistics.com.au/resources/content/2017/11/01/12-achievement-principles-in-extreme-ownership</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Bat_Forsaken"> /u/Bat_Forsaken </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jvosnf/true_leadership/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jvosnf/true_leadership/">[comments]</a></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jvosnf/true_leadership/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:25:25 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The State Our Movement</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jv4kox/the_state_our_movement/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<table> <tr><td> <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jv4kox/the_state_our_movement/"> <img src="https://b.thumbs.redditmedia.com/Izd0vaQf0n9ifUw9r4aOczawwAmwMudTR2URq9bbhng.jpg" alt="The State Our Movement" title="The State Our Movement" /> </a> </td><td> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Philly-South-Paw"> /u/Philly-South-Paw </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://i.redd.it/wec0gofnwkz51.jpg">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jv4kox/the_state_our_movement/">[comments]</a></span> </td></tr></table>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jv4kox/the_state_our_movement/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 03:25:23 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s happening the week of November 16 - 22</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jv18c3/whats_happening_the_week_of_november_16_22/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Please see our <a href="https://mailfence.com/pub/cal/denverprotestsdaily?a=1">new calendar</a> for the most complete list of upcoming vetted events.</p> <p>Events are color coded as follows:</p> <ul> <li>red: rally/protest/march</li> <li>purple: campaign (an event allowing activity spanning across several days)</li> <li>blue: government meeting</li> <li>yellow: education/training</li> <li>green: news</li> <li>orange: panel</li> <li>black: vigil</li> <li>pink: mutual aid</li> </ul> <h1>Wiki</h1> <p>To avoid repeating too much information from day to day, we&#39;ve created the beginnings of a wiki <a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/wiki/index">here</a>. Your feedback is much needed, as this is my (TaroPeril&#39;s) first experience with a reddit wiki. It contains links to livestreamers, your rights as a protestor, and more.</p> <h1>News</h1> <p>Please see <a href="https://twitter.com/nocapcoalition/status/1325867813215428608?s=21">this online fundraiser</a> to put together Mutual Aid/Winter Care Packages to distribute to our houseless neighbors in the Denver area! You can also <a href="https://no-capcoalition.org/events">sign up here</a> to volunteer to organize and distribute the packages.</p> <h1>Notable Events</h1> <h2>November 16</h2> <p><strong>4:30 PM - 6:30 PM</strong> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2812391055659964">Winter Survival – Full Court Press</a> (Facebook event)</p> <blockquote> <p><em>Organized by:</em> Coach MK Fleming and Wall of Moms Denver<br/> <em>Location:</em> 1431 Bannock St, Denver, CO 80202<br/> <em>Host-provided information:</em> Mayor Hancock is a disgrace, refusing to keep his campaign promise to assist the unhoused, and has unleashed a reign of terror on the most vulnerable in the form of sweeps, wasting our tax dollars during an economic recession. NO MORE. We need to be inside the meeting screaming at our reps and outside the building demonstrating <a href="/u/DenverCityCouncil">u/DenverCityCouncil</a>&#39;s utter failure to legislate. Community leaders will be demonstrating how to make survival items for the unhoused while I curse about how unnecessary this should be and demand that City Council press Hancock for #SolutionsNotSweeps in the 2021 budget, the first step to #defundthepolice and reallocate precious dollars to be invested in community SOLUTIONS.<br/> <em>Type of Event:</em> Rally/March</p> </blockquote> <p><strong>5:30 PM</strong> <a href="https://twitter.com/melanatedmic/status/1328088152976879617/photo/1">Melanated Mic Night</a> (Twitter post)</p> <blockquote> <p><em>Organized by:</em> Community-organized </p> <p><em>Location:</em> Instagram Live </p> <p><em>Host-provided information:</em> Melanated mic night gives a voice for this melanated table. No judgment, stereotypes, prejudice, or racism. All are welcome to join us in solidarity with all melanated humans. Bring your lawn chairs, let’s get comfortable together. </p> <p><em>Type of Event:</em> Arts/Education</p> </blockquote> <h2>November 21</h2> <p><strong>1:00 PM - 3:00 PM</strong> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2411035489021262">EMERGENCY ACTION: Eyes on Weiser! Justice for Elijah McClain!</a> (Facebook event)</p> <blockquote> <p><em>Organized by:</em> PSL </p> <p><em>Location:</em> Colorado State Capitol </p> <p><em>Host-provided information:</em> On June 25, under the pressure of mass protests against racist police killings, Governor Jared Polis issued an executive order which would open an independent investigation into Elijah McClain’s death, led by state Attorney General Phil Weiser. This was after Aurora District Attorney Dave Young declined to file any charges against the killers, then the city of Aurora opened a sham investigation led by a former cop which was terminated because it was plainly not “independent”. Now it is up to Phil Weiser to decide whether the cops and paramedics responsible for Elijah’s death will face any criminal charges. </p> <p>But just this week, Governor Polis quietly loosened the scope of the investigation, allowing Weiser to investigate for “offenses”, not just “criminal activity” related to Elijah’s death, opening up the possibility for him to come back with watered down charges against the killers, like we saw in Breonna Taylor’s case. Polis also took out the words that suggest someone caused the death of Elijah McClain. </p> <p>Polis must think that the movement isn’t paying attention, that we’ve been subdued by the repressive arrests of movement leaders, and now he can reel back his investigation without opposition in the streets. He is wrong. Join us for an emergency action to make it clear that we are still here and we are not going anywhere until we get justice for Elijah McClain! MASKS REQUIRED (OVER YOUR NOSE &amp; MOUTH!) &amp; PLEASE KEEP DISTANCE BETWEEN YOURSELF AND OTHERS.&quot; </p> <p><em>Type of Event:</em> Protest/Rally</p> </blockquote> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/denverprotestsdaily"> /u/denverprotestsdaily </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jv18c3/whats_happening_the_week_of_november_16_22/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jv18c3/whats_happening_the_week_of_november_16_22/">[comments]</a></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jv18c3/whats_happening_the_week_of_november_16_22/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 22:21:57 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The purpose of GA</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/juydl2/the_purpose_of_ga/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hi, I just wanted to say a few things about the GA that happened today that may be a bit controversial, but I have the best intentions so please hear me out. The biggest issue I have is that we spent over and hour and a half criticizing our fellow protestors. Is that the intention of GA? I understand that many people are against property destruction as a form of protest. This includes Trump supporters, instagram liberals, and apparently some of our own as well. I also understand that some people prefer we not be agitators. But at the same time should we really be telling other protestors what to do? Isn&#39;t trying to stop them mean suppressing their freedom of speech, just like the police do to us at every protest (peaceful or not)? I guess I never know what to expect from GA, but it was just tough to sit through a hour and a half of my allies ripping through my other allies (and really behind their back in a way). Ultimately I want more people showing up to protests and I feel like all this &quot;peace policing&quot; is doing the opposite. Again, is that the intention of GA?</p> <p>My solution? I think GA&#39;s should be almost entirely about future actions and actually ENCOURAGING people to come out. Even if its instagram liberals, it still gives us greater numbers, and ultimately those half-ass protestors will be affected by our leaders narratives. If you disagree with that idea, do you want people who are more &quot;intense&quot; to organize separately then? Again just trying to have an honest discussion. Is it crazy to think we should have a more positive energy when it comes to dealing with people who actually agree with us at the end of the day?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/SwimPhillips"> /u/SwimPhillips </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/juydl2/the_purpose_of_ga/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/juydl2/the_purpose_of_ga/">[comments]</a></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/juydl2/the_purpose_of_ga/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 19:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Location changed to Denver capital. Hope y&#39;all can make it!</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/ju5fgw/location_changed_to_denver_capital_hope_yall_can/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<table> <tr><td> <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/ju5fgw/location_changed_to_denver_capital_hope_yall_can/"> <img src="https://b.thumbs.redditmedia.com/M63mbxImvjckWk2kFn8q2fG3oZyxjZROFtngnAtUcSE.jpg" alt="Location changed to Denver capital. Hope y'all can make it!" title="Location changed to Denver capital. Hope y'all can make it!" /> </a> </td><td> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/skidwitch"> /u/skidwitch </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://i.redd.it/dst9z0xeo8z51.jpg">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/ju5fgw/location_changed_to_denver_capital_hope_yall_can/">[comments]</a></span> </td></tr></table>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/ju5fgw/location_changed_to_denver_capital_hope_yall_can/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 10:17:50 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City of Aurora files public court denial of wrongdoing in Elijah McClain case</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtyolv/city_of_aurora_files_public_court_denial_of/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><a href="https://kdvr.com/news/local/city-of-aurora-files-public-court-denial-of-wrongdoing-in-elijah-mcclain-case/">https://kdvr.com/news/local/city-of-aurora-files-public-court-denial-of-wrongdoing-in-elijah-mcclain-case/</a> </p> <p>AURORA, Colo. (KDVR) — Attorneys for the City of Aurora filed recent court paperwork denying responsibility for the death of Elijah McClain.</p> <p>“The death of Elijah McClain is a tragedy; however, this tragedy was not caused by any acts or omissions of the (Aurora Police Department) Defendants. APD Defendants deny that they used excessive force on Mr. McClain in violation of the Fourth Amendment, that they denied him equal protection of the law under the Fourteenth Amendment and that they caused his death by batter or neglect,” a filing in federal court said.</p> <p>The scheduling order, filed in late October, also claimed officers were “justified” in stopping McClain as he was walking home and in their use of the carotid hold, a subduing technique that is now banned by the City of Aurora. </p> <p>It also denies wrongdoing on behalf of the Aurora Fire Rescue paramedics who sedated McClain with ketamine before he died.</p> <p>A coroner who ruled McClain’s death to be undetermined said his rough interaction with police and the ketamine administration could not be ruled out as contributors to his death.</p> <p>The Aurora Fire defendants “deny any negligent, intentionally tortious, or otherwise unlawful conduct in connection with their treatment of Plaintiff McClain on August 24, 2019. At all times relevant to the allegations…all actions by defendants…were conducted in good faith and with the believe that their actions were lawful, reasonable, and consistent with their duties and obligations as firefighter paramedics for the City of Aurora under local, state, and federal law and regulations,” the filing stated.</p> <p>The City also argued that some defendants could be entitled to use the defense of qualified immunity, that they were unaware that their actions may have been a violation of a plaintiff’s rights.</p> <p>“All of them murdered an innocent young man, and yet, they say, ‘It’s a tragedy,’ but none of them were responsible for it. Well, that’s a lot of BS,” said Mari Newman, the attorney who represents McClain’s family.</p> <p>Newman laid out her arguments in the same filing, as well as estimates for the amount of financial damages she hopes to seek on behalf of the McClain family. The medical costs totaled close to $250,000, and she estimated the losses of McClain’s future earnings could be as high as $3.5 million.</p> <p>“These calculable damages are the tip of the iceberg,” said Newman, explaining that there are likely tens of millions of dollars in other damages she hopes to collect for his family’s emotional losses and the experience McClain endured during the incident.</p> <p>“The biggest thing, I think, is the emotional pain and suffering that Elijah went through as this 18 minutes of torture unfolded. It’s not like it was just sort of a quick and painless death. It was a prolonged and petrifying experience where he knew he was going to die, and he was begging for his life,” she said.</p> <p>Newman also said she would be seeking punitive damages.</p> <p>“We recognize the tragic nature of the death of Elijah McClain. However, the city disagrees with the broad characterizations expressed in the lawsuit, including some that are completely unrelated to the facts of this case,” said Michael Bryant, a spokesperson for the City of Aurora. “The statements in the scheduling order, which is a required filing in all federal cases, are based on a legal view of this matter relying on applicable laws and court decisions. A critical review of our organization is underway and we have made, and will continue to make, changes to how Police serve all people in our city that are responsive to what the community wants and deserves. Because of the ongoing litigation, we are unable to provide further information about the city’s legal actions in this case.”</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/kellypell"> /u/kellypell </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtyolv/city_of_aurora_files_public_court_denial_of/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtyolv/city_of_aurora_files_public_court_denial_of/">[comments]</a></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtyolv/city_of_aurora_files_public_court_denial_of/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 01:17:20 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Million MAGA March</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtxdf4/million_maga_march/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Stay aware tomorrow if you plan to counter protest</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/your_local_manager"> /u/your_local_manager </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtxdf4/million_maga_march/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtxdf4/million_maga_march/">[comments]</a></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtxdf4/million_maga_march/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 23:32:55 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMERGENCY ACTION: Eyes on Weiser! Justice for Elijah McClain!</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtsthv/emergency_action_eyes_on_weiser_justice_for/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<table> <tr><td> <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtsthv/emergency_action_eyes_on_weiser_justice_for/"> <img src="https://b.thumbs.redditmedia.com/MYQrSOWyZwLnnN9sxg8bBy3CHs3ZTE83ObDi7BX_TvU.jpg" alt="EMERGENCY ACTION: Eyes on Weiser! Justice for Elijah McClain!" title="EMERGENCY ACTION: Eyes on Weiser! Justice for Elijah McClain!" /> </a> </td><td> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/pinkottah"> /u/pinkottah </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2411035489021262/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtsthv/emergency_action_eyes_on_weiser_justice_for/">[comments]</a></span> </td></tr></table>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtsthv/emergency_action_eyes_on_weiser_justice_for/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 18:12:32 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged with pointing laser at Denver police helicopter</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtnvxv/man_charged_with_pointing_laser_at_denver_police/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<table> <tr><td> <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtnvxv/man_charged_with_pointing_laser_at_denver_police/"> <img src="https://a.thumbs.redditmedia.com/PDv5VuL1YxhliU92xJ5wtGmZYqEbw-jO7S-ubf6wXt0.jpg" alt="Man charged with pointing laser at Denver police helicopter" title="Man charged with pointing laser at Denver police helicopter" /> </a> </td><td> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/demonni"> /u/demonni </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Man-charged-with-pointing-laser-at-Denver-police-15723605.php">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtnvxv/man_charged_with_pointing_laser_at_denver_police/">[comments]</a></span> </td></tr></table>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtnvxv/man_charged_with_pointing_laser_at_denver_police/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 13:36:50 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showing Up for Racial Justice - SURJ Denver Call To Action</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtj9kx/showing_up_for_racial_justice_surj_denver_call_to/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<table> <tr><td> <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtj9kx/showing_up_for_racial_justice_surj_denver_call_to/"> <img src="https://b.thumbs.redditmedia.com/NSBW7yvsTbFiWmdOaPciH9Yy8Diq7ygMUj24nOeLGEw.jpg" alt="Showing Up for Racial Justice - SURJ Denver Call To Action" title="Showing Up for Racial Justice - SURJ Denver Call To Action" /> </a> </td><td> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/pinkottah"> /u/pinkottah </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.facebook.com/NDenverSocialJustice/posts/2756977271235160">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtj9kx/showing_up_for_racial_justice_surj_denver_call_to/">[comments]</a></span> </td></tr></table>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jtj9kx/showing_up_for_racial_justice_surj_denver_call_to/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 09:50:27 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So uh, police shot and killed a man they describe as “unresponsive” - Little information released nearly a week after Glendale Police shot and killed a man on Colorado Boulevard</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jt1t7y/so_uh_police_shot_and_killed_a_man_they_describe/</link>
      <description></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<table> <tr><td> <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jt1t7y/so_uh_police_shot_and_killed_a_man_they_describe/"> <img src="https://b.thumbs.redditmedia.com/DZcLnDVArRs1s2l01X-m2YE5t2CROa_G5ahaW2hBEFM.jpg" alt="So uh, police shot and killed a man they describe as “unresponsive” - Little information released nearly a week after Glendale Police shot and killed a man on Colorado Boulevard" title="So uh, police shot and killed a man they describe as “unresponsive” - Little information released nearly a week after Glendale Police shot and killed a man on Colorado Boulevard" /> </a> </td><td> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/mmmillerism"> /u/mmmillerism </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.9news.com/article/news/crime/little-information-released-nearly-week-after-glendale-police-shot-killed-man/73-ebbd83ca-458a-4670-8c62-719d5a5527da">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jt1t7y/so_uh_police_shot_and_killed_a_man_they_describe/">[comments]</a></span> </td></tr></table>]]></content:encoded>
      <author>r/DenverProtests</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/DenverProtests/comments/jt1t7y/so_uh_police_shot_and_killed_a_man_they_describe/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 12:54:14 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>